hi my name is Vicente Romero I work at
嗨，我叫维森特·罗梅罗（Vicente Romero），我在
the job Hudson group at coracle and
哈德森在甲骨文的工作团队和
today I'm going to meet an introduction
今天我要见一个介绍
to Jeff three-two-three local burial
给杰夫三二三葬
syntax for another parameters
其他参数的语法
in this section we're going to talk
在本节中，我们将讨论
about local variable syntax for lambda
关于lambda的局部变量语法
parameter which is a new feature
参数，这是一个新功能
included in Java SE 11
包含在Java SE 11中
this feature is related to previous
此功能与以前的功能有关
feature name local variable type
功能名称局部变量类型
inference which had a broader goal as it
推论有更广泛的目标
affected local variables which are in
受影响的局部变量
general more frequent than the
一般比
parameters this new feature were talking
这个新功能正在讨论的参数
about the employee changes to the Java
关于员工对Java所做的更改
language specification and tools like
语言规范和工具，例如
jealousy and each shell local burlock
嫉妒和每个贝壳当地的伯洛克
type inference extended type inference
类型推断扩展类型推断
to the corrections of local variables
局部变量的校正
with initializers i've shown in the
与我已经在
provided example the compiler and infer
提供示例的编译器并进行推断
the types of local variables with the
局部变量的类型与
from the initializer without additional
从初始值设定项开始
information from the user this leads to
来自用户的信息，这导致
less ceremony but keeps Java full static
较少的仪式，但保持Java完全静态
type safety others local variable syntax
类型安全其他局部变量语法
for nano parameters are in a nutshell
纳米参数概述
uniformity it aligns the syntax of the
一致性，它使
formal parameter declaration in an
形式参数声明
especially type land expression with the
特别是用
syntax of a local variable declaration
局部变量声明的语法
ensured the two decorations shown shown
确保所示的两个装饰
here are allowed by the Java compiler
Java编译器允许在这里
and are considered equivalent
并被认为是等效的
as an additional benefit now
作为额外的好处
annotations can be applied to lambda
注释可以应用于lambda
formal without losing Bertie as we can
正式而不会失去Bertie
see in this example there are some
看到在这个例子中有一些
restrictions to the use of the local
限制使用当地
variable syntax for the parameters
参数的可变语法
though it can only be used for the
尽管它只能用于
formal parameters of increasingly type
形式参数越来越多
lambda and is used for one for one
lambda，用于一对一
parameter in an expression it should be
表达式中的参数应为
used for roadman as a consequence the
因此用于守门员
following example are considered legal
以下示例被认为是合法的
by the compiler there are some
通过编译器有一些
additional restrictions for example he
其他限制，例如他
was decided that should in order to
决定应该为了
maintain the brevity of the shorthand
保持简明扼要
syntax the following example is
语法下面的例子是
considered illegal by the Java language
被Java语言视为非法
and compiler Oracle is the steward of
编译器Oracle是
Java providing a large amount of
Java提供了大量的
development engineering found in the
的开发工程
Java platform and open JDK Oracle
Java平台和开放JDK Oracle
provides living class premium supports
提供生活水平的优质支持
for a low cost easy to purchase with
易于购买的低成本
simple pricing tiers and with that thank
简单的定价层级，并感谢
you for watching
你看
you
您